我在考虑今晚的约会
Oh, hey. I was wondering about date night tonight.
你想不想就在家呆着呢
Um, do you want to just stay in?
你明白我的意思吧
'Cause you know what that means.
-浪漫晚餐  然后看国土安全  -滚床单
- Romantic dinner and Homeland? - Sex on the couch.
-你的想法更好  -其实看国土安全也不错
- Or your thing. - Actually, Homeland sounds great.
还是你的想法更好
Or your thing.
尼克
Hey, Nick, um...
我昨晚跟弗格森洗澡的时候
Last night when Furguson and I were in the shower,
我恍然大悟了
I had an epiphany.
是时候回到现实了
It's time to get back in the game.
我该去见见女人
You know, meet some women.
人类的女人
Human women.
-人类  还有其他类的女人么  -女人
- Human? Is there any other kind? - Human.
我想今晚你能不能帮我照看弗格森
Anyway, I was wondering if you'd watch Furguson tonight
我想出去跟工作伙伴们喝几杯
while I go out for some drinks with some work buddies.
就一会就好  你记得6点给他吃药就行
Just for a little while. You just gotta give him a pill at 6:00.
-我们今晚要约会  -杰茜
- We're having date night tonight. - Jess...
温斯顿要出去见女人了
Winston wants to go out to meet human women.
还不带猫
Without the cat.
哦  这样哦
Oh, yep, yep.
好的  好的  尼克会照看你的猫
Yep, yep. Nick will watch the cat.
有个问题  喂药是从嘴喂还是从屁屁喂
Question, are those mouth pills or butt pills?
就一片药
Just one pill.
从屁屁喂
Just one butt pill.
-给你  -不用了  我不想碰它
- Here you are. - Nah, I'm not touching that thing.
不想  好吧
No? Okay.
-谢了  哥们  -客气
- Thanks, man. - Yeah. You got it.
你们今晚就在家了吗
Hey, guys. Just hanging at home tonight?
不啊  我们要约会
No, actually, we have a date tonight.
我刚做了酥皮水果馅饼
'Cause I just made some cobbler.
桃子馅的
Some peach cobbler
我还弄了香草冰淇淋
and slow-churned vanilla bean ice cream,
今晚教练要约会希希
and Coach is asking Cece out on a date tonight, and...
谁想来一口吗
does anybody want a bite of this, 'cause it's...?
刚出锅的哦
It's fresh out of the oven.
烫爆了
It's piping hot!
但愿教练提前跟你打招呼了
Well, I hope Coach at least ran this by you first.
教练来找我了  很讲义气
Coach came over, he followed the bro code.
我们聊得挺好的
Actually went really well.
我正要找你呢
Yeah. Just the man I wanted to see.
-那正好  -是啊
- You found me. -Yeah, I did.
亲  我有个问题问你
I got a question for you, playa.
放马过来吧
Drop the bomb, man!
我能约希希去约会吗
Can I ask Cece out on a date?
好啊  等等  你说什么
Yeah! Wait, what?
对希希是大好事啊  教练那么帅
Wait, that's so great for Cece. Coach is super hot.
最佳损友
Wrong crowd.
我看出来了
I see that now.
尽管如此  你已经跟希希吹了
Be that as it may, you blew it with Cece,
你应该不介意这事儿吧
so you have to be fine with this.
-我可以啊  -真的吗
- I am. - You are?
-我绝对没问题  -是吗
- I promise I am. - You are?
-我百分之百没事  -你没事吗
- 100% fine. - You're fine?
-我完全没事的  -真的么
- Yeah, I'm absolutely fine. -Really?
这对希希好  对教练也好  皆大欢喜啊
It's good for Cece, it's good for Coach, it's good for America.
可能又弄出一个泰格伍兹呢
Who knows? We might even get another Tiger Woods out of this situation.
那多好啊
Wouldn't that be nice?
我可能就是想多了
I'm probably getting ahead of myself.
希希还不一定答应呢
Who knows if Cece will even say yes?
她答应了
She said yes!
我们今晚要去斯台普斯中心看球
We're going to the Staples Center to watch a game tonight.
你确定你没事吗
Are you still... Are you cool with this?
只要你说出那个词
I mean, 'cause all you have to do is say the word, man,
我一定收手
and I'll back off, for real.
不啊
N... No, man.
加油  就约她
Come on. Date that thing.
-好啊  -多约几次
- Yeah! All right! -Yeah! And then date it again.
-可不光是约个会  -约个一整晚哦
- It's not gonna date itself. - Yeah, date it all night long.
我有点紧张了
I'm kind of nervous!
没错  我紧张了
Yeah, I'm nervous.
我非常紧张
Yeah, I'm really nervous. Um...
她那么美  又超级酷
I mean, she's beautiful and she's super cool.
你简直无法想象
And it's just, like... Like, you don't even know.
-我百分百知道  -没错  你知道
- I 100% know. - Yes, you kno... You know.
因为我  她都悔婚了
She stopped the wedding because of me, so I'm just saying.
然后我却辜负了她  因为我自己的原因
And then I ruined it 'cause I had my own thing.
玛丽亚跟我分手
Malia broke up with me and that kind of,
弄得我可不淡定了
like, threw my head for a loop,
-所以我现在可脆弱了  -别  别担心
- so I'm super vulnerable right now. - Oh, wait. Don't-don't worry.
就好像  我也不知道
It's like... I don't know.
我觉得特没安全感
Think I'm feeling kind of insecure.
别这样  你可是教练啊
Come on. You're Coach.
-你是独一无二的教练  -没错
- You're the Coach. - Yeah.
你可是一流的  记住  你是一流的
You're the prize. Remember, you're the prize.
你是一流的
You're the prize.
我可是教练
I'm Coach!
没错  你可是教练
Yeah, you're Coach.
-那她可是手到擒来  -好吧
- She doesn't stand a chance! - Oh, yeah, well...
我要好好调教调教她
She's gonna get it good!
你其实可以不那么操之过急的
Yeah! Or you could take it slow!
-不  我要提枪上阵  -你要提枪上阵
- Nah, I'm gunning it! - Oh, oh! Y-You're gonna gun it.
-我要提枪上战场  -你来真的吗
- I am gunning it. Yes. - You're gonna gun it for real?
头等舱的屁股今晚要坐在教练牌椅子上
That first-class ass is sitting in Coach tonight.
收起小桌板  哥要带她起飞啦
And best believe, my seat will be in an upright and locked position.
谢了  施密特
Thanks, Schmidt.
弟兄们
Oh... boy.
他要提枪上阵了
He's gonna gun it.
不知道你们听到没
I don't know if you heard that,
但他说他要提枪上阵了
but he said he's going to gun it.
-他真的不像没事  -在他说
- He's really not fine. - When he says,
"我没事"的时候  他一定会有事的
"I'm fine," He's about to get un-fine.
施密特
Aw, Schmidters.
一定会有别的开放表演场有更坚固的凳子
There's gonna be other open mics with sturdier stools.
我没事
I'm fine.
我知道你没事
I know you're fine.
到时候他们就能见识到你的说唱水准
Then they'll see your rap skills. Then...
住手  你刚刚说你没事的
Hey. Stop! You just said you were fine!
你刚刚说你没事的
You just said you were fine!
让我死吧
Let me die!
我了解施密特
I know Schmidt.
他会全力去破坏那场约会的
He's gonna try and stop that date from happening.
-好吧  -所以只能把他控制住
- Okay. - So the strategy is containment.
-好吧  -我们得把他锁起来
- Okay. - Okay? We got to lock him up.
像对婴儿一样分散他的注意力
Distract him like a baby.
要是他不乖  我们就动用武力
If he gets out of line, we got to get physical.
我们要对婴儿动武吗
We're gonna get physical with a baby?
别质疑我  我可是专业的
Please don't question me. I'm a pro.
或者我们可以帮他走出来
Or we could help him move on.
带他出去  让他喝醉  没准能遇上新欢呢
Take him out, get him drunk, maybe meet someone new?
不  我们得把他关在安全的地方
No. We just got to keep him in a safe place.
真希望我弄到了那狗笼
I wish I had that dog cage.
-搞没搞错  -看到有狗笼卖你就买一个
- What? - When you see a dog cage for sale, you buy it.
杰茜  今晚又泡汤了  真的很对不起
Hey, Jess, about tonight, I'm so sorry.
没事的没事的
Yeah. No, it's okay.
要约会的话可以等我嫁...
We'll have date night when we're marrie...
-个乌哎  乖乖隆个咚  -你刚刚是说
- da, burp a durp a durp. - What did you just...
假日  等到圣诞假日的时候
Merry. When we're very merry Christmas.
算了不管了
All right, moving on.
我仔细想了想教练和希希
I'm having second thoughts about Coach and Cece.
也许我该阻止他们约会
Maybe I should stop their date.
变聪明了
Smarten up!
谢谢你
Thank you. Um...
你弄到那个狗笼了吗
did you get a chance to get that, uh... the dog cage?
-没  我觉得这不好  -你没弄到吗
- No. I feel bad. - You didn't?
-那是个办法  -我知道
- That was the solution. - I know it was.
是的  杰茜  我刚刚打电话给他了
Yeah, Jess, so I j... I just... I just buzzed him up.
我  他约我出去  我答应了
I... He asked me out on a date, and I said yes.
反正我们俩都刚刚分手
We're both going through a breakup right now,
这挺好的  不是吗
which is good, right?
没错
Totally.
提枪上阵
Gun it. You gun it!
他到啦
He's here.
顶多跟他亲亲抱抱
Don't go past second base.
好的  拜拜
Okay. Bye.
你看上去...  真美
Wow. Uh, y-you look... amazing.
你看上去...
You look...
太美了
This.
我举大拇指因为你看上去...
I give you this 'cause you look...
这个  这个和这个
This, this and this.
全都送给你  不  这样不大好...
I'll give you all these. No. Not...
我...  能去看球我好激动
I'm, uh... I'm really excited about the game.
好耶
Yeah!
很好  很好
Yeah. Yeah.
我去拿包
I'm gonna go get my purse.
看看你自己
Look at you!
你是最棒的  你是最棒的
You're the prize! You're the prize!
振作起来
Get it together.
你好吗
Hey. What's up, man?
咋样  咋样  咋样
That's what's up, that's what's up, that's what's up.
真的很谢谢你们陪我
Really appreciate this, guys.
你们饿了吗
Are you guys hungry?
-一直很饿  -没错
- Always. - Yeah.
太好了  我去斯台普斯中心买点吃的
Great. I'm gonna go get some food from the Staples Center.
位于洛杉矶中心城区的多功能体育中心
放松  冷静点
Hey, easy. Chill out.
你是对的  你是对的  明智的决定
You're right, you're right. Great call.
你好  温斯顿
Hey, Winston.
你怎么啦
Hey. What happened to you?
我以为你去派对了
I thought you were supposed to go to a party.
是啊  时间久得
Yeah, it's been so long
我都忘了该如何与女士聊天了
that I think I forgot how to talk to women.
你从未好奇过这里是否有人杀过人吗
You ever wonder if someone in here has killed someone?
弗格森是他的名字  没错  他是我的猫
Furguson is his name. Yeah, he's my cat.
你看他戴着牛仔帽
Here's him in a cowboy hat.
天呐  亲爱的  你的脚是有多大啊
Good Lord, darling, how big are your feet?
你知道吗  没关系
You know what? It's fine.
我可以独自过一生
I'll be alone my whole life.
汉克・阿伦每次全垒打时也是一个人
You know, Hank Aaron was alone for every home run he hit.
只要还有弗格森陪着我
As long as I got Furguson.
说到这  我的猫呢
Speaking of which, where is that cat?
弗格森
Furguson!
这就奇怪了  我一叫他就会过来的
That's strange. He usually comes when I call him.
尼克  你是不是忘了关窗户
Nick, you left the window open?
天呐  这下完了
Oh, my God. No.
-尼克  -什么事
- Nick! - What?
他一直想要踢开窗户去抓鸽子的
You know he always trying to kick it with those pigeons.
尼克  是你放跑他的
Nick, you let him out.
我不是有意的  只是不小心打开了窗户
I did... I didn't mean to. I just opened the window.
兄弟  我就拜托你一件事
Man, I asked you to do one thing!
-温斯顿  我很抱歉  -这是你的错
- Winston, I'm really sorry. - This is your fault, man!
我很内疚  温斯顿
I feel terrible, Winston.
你得帮我找回他
You're gonna help me find him!
温斯顿  别走啊  温斯顿...
Winston, don't leave... Winston...
好吧  我来了  兄弟
Okay, I'm coming, buddy.
杰茜  不好意思  你得
Jess, I'm sorry, but you're gonna
-留下来看着施密特  -不
- have to stay here and keep an eye on Schmidt. - No.
你不能留我跟他单独在一起
You can't leave me here with him.
没错  她说得对
No, she's right.
你可不能这么做  万一我失控了呢
You can't do that. What if it gets rough?
尼克  我能感觉到他正在水深火热之中
Nick, he is in pain. I can feel it.
-你走试试看  -留下来
- Don't you go! - Stay!
我好怕怕  哥们
I am so scared, man!
那你想要我怎么做  杰茜
What do you want me to do, Jess?
-留下  -你敢走试试看  -别吵啦
- Stay. - Don't you dare go. - Everybody settle!
这是我的错  温斯顿  我跟你一起去
Look, this is my fault. Winston, I'm coming with you.
好的
Okay.
施密特  振作起来吧
Schmidt, just get it together.
杰茜  我很抱歉  你在这看好他
Jess, I'm sorry. Just keep him here
将他的注意力从约会上移开  我得走了
and keep his mind off the date. I got to go.
抱歉啊
I'm sorry.
我们走
We got to go.
去找那只该死的猫吧
Let's find that damn cat!
你觉得教练和希希现在正在做什么
What do you think Coach and Cece are doing right now?
-我可不知道  -他们可能已经坐下来
- I don't know. - They probably just sat down.
第一次互相摸大腿了
Touching thighs for the first time.
-我要去阻止他们的约会  -不
- I'm gonna go stop that date! - No!
你就这么一点点本事吗
Is that literally all you have?
天呐  我们完蛋了
Oh, my God, we're screwed.
-尼克  -尼克
- Nick! - Nick!
想想看
Uh, think.
教练给我留了破绽
Coach gave me an out.
他说  "只要你说出那个词  我就收手"
He said, "Just say the word and it's off."
不管了  我要去说出那个词
And you know what? I'm just gonna say the word.
不要  别这样
No! No!
你去打电话  你去跟他说
You call, you say the word.
不  施密特
No, Schmidt!
天呐  你不能这样对希希
God, you can't do that to Cece.
她刚跨过你这道坎
She's just starting to move on.
我们只要熬过今晚就好了
All we have to do is get through the night.
只要熬过今晚就好
Just get through the night.
你只要不去想她就好
Just have to get your mind off her.
你想先做什么
What do you want to start with?
Play it now
Play it now, my baby
Cracklin' Rosie, get on by
你这是  这是干嘛
What's- what's happening?
也许你不该穿鞋子跳  我也不知道
Maybe just go no shoes. I don't know.
这是十年级的时候  所以
Okay, and this one's tenth grade, so...
这个是伊万・G写的
This one's from Evan G.
伊万・G是水球队的队长
Evan G. Was the captain of the water polo team.
"你好呀杰茜  我们都喜欢午餐"
"Hey, Jess, we both like lunch."
这倒是事实
That's true.
靠过来一点  兄弟
Oh, lean in... aw, dude...
Play it now, play it now
My baby
Cracklin' Rosie, get on board
《律师本色》剧情
卡穆琳・曼海姆给一个被狂欢节小丑骚扰的女人
Camryn Manheim represents a woman who was heckled
做代表  然后迪伦・麦克德莫特说...
by a carnival clown, and Dylan McDermott says...
-我没法不想希希  -行
- I can't stop thinking about Cece! - Okay!
尼克还说这有用呢  坐下
Nick said this would work. Sit down.
-别想希希了  -我坐下了
- Stop thinking about Cece. - I'm gonna sit down.
你看这皮革
Look at this leather.
它是褐色的  这么的光滑
It's so smooth, brown.
就像希希一样
It's just like Cece.
这样说真奇怪
That's weird.
你说得对  我该躺一会儿
You're right. I'm just gonna lay down for a little bit.
好的
Okay.
这感觉太棒了
Oh, yeah, this feels good.
行了
Okay.
你在做什么  施密特
What are you doing, Schmidt?
-什么都没做  你走吧  -不不不
- Nothing, just go. - No, no, no, no.
-你走吧  -好的
- Just go away. - Okay...
施密特  听我说
Schmidt, hey.
不行  我得把你弄出去
No! We're getting you out of here,
我们再给你找一个妹子  好吗
and we're gonna get you a new woman, okay?
尼克说了要待在家里
Nick said to stay home.
尼克不会什么都知道的  施密特
Well, Nick doesn't know everything, Schmidt.
别这样了  这太恶心人了
And please stop this. This is so disgusting.
我都没法直视你了
I can't even look at you.
这太恶心了  你这样很奇怪
Come on, this is gross. This is getting really weird.
拜托  让我再亲一口
Please! Just one more kiss!
你亲的是家具  蠢货
No, you're kissing a sectional, you dummy!
好吧
All right.
这样是对的  你做得对
That was the right move. You did good.
弗格森  弗格森
Furguson! Furguson!
弗格森
Furguson!
快回来  兄弟
Come here, buddy!
快来啊  你这个小坏蛋
Come on, you little son of a bitch!
我们应该再围着公园转一圈
We should do another lap around the park.
我猜现在那些玩飞碟的小破孩应该走了
I bet those mean-ass kids playing Frisbee are gone by now.
温斯顿  我们所有地方都找过了
Winston... we've looked everywhere.
你要干...  温斯顿
What are you do...? Winston.
该死
Damn it!
我真不该去那个派对的
I should've never gone to that party.
不  派对是个好东西
Nah, the party was a good thing.
-你应该多参加点派对  -真的吗
- You should go to more parties. - Really?
我被  我也不知道
I got shot down by, I don't know,
16个女人拒绝了
16 or so different women.
然后我回家来却发现
And then I come home to find out
你弄丢了我最好的朋友
that you have misplaced my best friend.
-弗格森变成你最好的朋友了  -对
- Furguson's your best friend now? - Yes!
你知道自己在说什么吗
Would you listen to yourself?
太可悲了
This is pathetic.
"可悲"有点太严重了
"Pathetic" is harsh.
我不是...
I didn't mean...
朋友才不会说朋友可悲呢
Friends don't call friends pathetic.
如果朋友和猫洗澡
Well, what do friends do
他的朋友该说什么呢
when their other friend is taking a shower with a cat?
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait!
我收到一条短信
I just got a text.
有人找到他了
Somebody found him.
真的吗
No way!
-对  -弗格森
- Yes. - Furguson?
对  别拍手
Yes! Don't do that at all.
如果猫还活着  我们就和解了
If that cat's alive, we're made up.
你喜欢那货吗
How you liking that merch?
这个
Oh, it's...
这个非常棒  谢谢
it's great, thanks.
没错  没错
Yeah, yeah.
想吃咸味脆饼吧
You want a pretzel?
不用了  这样很好  谢谢
No, I'm-I'm fine, thanks.
刚才不是提问  帅哥
It wasn't a question. Hey, yo, slice!
给我来七个热乎的
Let me get about seven of them hot things!
你怕我没钱吗
You worried about the money?
没问题  我有钱  宝贝
It's cool, I got it, babe.
教练今年收成好
Coach had a good year today.
好吧  我同意跟你约会的时候
Yeah, when I-I agreed to go out with you,
可没想到这种事
this isn't exactly what I expected.
我知道  大家都这么说  大家都这么说
I know, I hear that a lot, I hear that a lot.
看这个
Ha-ha! Look at that.
教练收到好多短信啊
Coach is blowing up.
我来...
I'll just...
谢谢
Thanks.
该死
Damn it.
我没法跟这些人渣瞎混
I can't mingle with this trash.
曾经沧海难为水
I've been to the mountaintop.
好了  听着  看着我
Okay, look. Look at me.
你要向前看  原来那个施密特哪去了
You are moving on. Now, where's the old Schmidt?
我刚搬来的时候  你可是来者不拒的
When I moved into the loft, you used to pull so many ladies.
你从前就是个传奇
You were legendary.
那时  飓风施密特无坚不摧
That year, uh, Hurricane Schmidt did-did demolish
-横扫很多海滩社团  -对
- a number of beach communities. - Right.
好了  咱们去跟那边那个姑娘聊聊
All right, we're gonna go talk to this girl over here.
她还在用翻盖手机  杰茜
She's on a flip phone, Jess.
她要么很穷  要么就是穿越了
I mean, she's either poor or a time traveler.
你好  这是我的朋友施密特
Hi! This is my friend Schmidt.
他又可爱又聪明
And he's sweet and he's smart.
他的工作我不太懂
And he has a job that I don't really understand,
但是薪水应该很高
but seems to pay him well.
-施密特  坐下  -好
- Schmidt, sit down. - Okay.
我不打搅你们俩了
I'm gonna give you two a moment.
听我说  你是个美丽的女人
Look, you're a beautiful woman.
换种活法  我们肯定会成情人  但是
In another life, we certainly would've been lovers, but...
我的灵魂伴侣
my soul mate
正跟另一个男人玩"烟花"[烈性鸡尾酒]
is at a Sparks game right now with another man.
我得去找她
I need to go get her.
-你真可怜...  -请别打断我
- Oh, you poor thing... - Please don't interrupt me.
看到那边那个一直偷瞟的女人吗
Now, do you see that bug-eyed woman over there?
我得把她甩开
I need to ditch her
这样我才能实现自己的命运
so that I can go fulfill my destiny.
她看别处的时候跟我说一声
Now, tell me when she looks away.
正在看我们
Not now.
还不行  稍等
Not now. Wait.
就现在
Now.
只可惜相遇太晚
What might've been.
施密特  站住
Hey, Schmidt! No!
你猜他会变成什么样
What do you think he's gonna look like?
我也不知道  我只想带他回去
I don't know, I wanna get him back.
发现他的时候他正趴在台阶下
Found him under the steps
吃死浣熊的眼珠子
eating a dead raccoon's eyeball.
你的猫是个疯子
Your cat's a psycho.
我的小宝贝享受到美味了吗
Oh, did my baby have a tasty treat?
弗格森  我想死你了  小伙伴
Furguson, I missed you so much, little buddy.
他俩心有灵犀
They're very connected, those two.
我懂  我自己也养了一头野兽
I can relate. Got a beast of my own.
霍金亲  醒醒
Hodgkiss, wake up.
我们有伴了
We got company.
-那是只松鼠吗  -松鼠  这是仓鼠
- Is that a squirrel? - Squirrel? It's a hamster.
尼克  你知道松鼠长什么样子
Nick, you know what a squirrel looks like.
你去过户外  哥们
Okay, you've been outside, man.
我在努力辨别它的气味
Trying to just figure out the smell, I guess.
这家伙最听话了
This guy's the best.
我宁愿和他一起在家看实习医生格蕾
I'd rather stay home and watch Grey's with him
也不愿去酒吧
than go out to some bar,
试着讨好那些打扮的像伐木工人一样的笨蛋
try to impress some douche bag dressed like a lumberjack.
我已经对男人没兴趣了
I am done chasing men.
我懂
I hear that.
我也对女人没兴趣了
I am so done chasing women.
那真是太糟了
That's too bad.
太可惜了
Yeah, it's too bad.
你们饿吗
You guys hungry?
-不用了  谢谢  -我想吃点
- Oh, no, but thank you very much for the offer. - I could eat.
温斯顿  你喜欢吃博洛尼亚肠吗
Winston, do you like bologna?
就是你要先扒掉外面的包装
It's the kind you have to peel the wrapper off
才能吃到肉的那种
just to get to the meat.
那你有杯装的布丁吗
And do you have pudding in a cup?
我的杯子从来不装布丁
I never have pudding in a cup.
是吗
No.
她这么说是好事还是坏事
Is that a good thing or a bad thing that she doesn't?
是好事
That's a good thing.
我不知道你俩在搞什么
You know, I don't know what's going on here.
寻找斯台普斯中心
Find Staples Center!
寻找膝部医疗补给
Finding Starples Medical Supply.
不是  你这笨蛋手机
No, you dumb pocket robot!
丹轴架橡胶伐木机
Dan Plummer Rubber Stumpers.
你现在都开始瞎编了
Aah! Now you're just making up words!
这根本就不是个地名
That's not even a place!
去你的
Damn you!
少女伍斯特郡酱
Maiden Worcestershire Sauce.
巧克力
Huh. Chocolate.
你好
Hi, there.
我要破坏一场约会  不想空着手去
I'm ruining a date, and I don't want to show up empty-handed.
我要三个甜牛奶巧克力
I will take three of the, ooh, the dulce de leches.
再来点焦糖的
How about some caramels?
你们有没有能代表"抱歉我出轨了
Do you have anything that says "I'm sorry for cheating on you.
请不要和我朋友上床"的品种
Please don't sleep with my friend"?
当然没有  很好
Of course you don't. Wonderful.
看这些试吃品
Ooh, look at that-- samples.
你和谁短信呢
Wha...? Who are you texting right now?
你说什么呢
Uh, wh-what are you talking about?
我没在发短信  我只是...
I'm not texting. I was just, uh...
你此时此刻就在发短信
You're texting right now.
不  我只是...
Nah, I'm just, uh...
无论你在和谁发
Okay, you know what? Whoever you are texting,
如果你想和他们一起的话
if you want to be with them,
你应该走开去和他们一起
you should just go off and be with them.
你真爱吃醋
You're so jealous.
好吧  老娘够了
Okay, yeah, you know what-- that's it!
老娘不伺候了
That is the last straw!
拜拜您那
I'm out of here.
希希...
Cece...
伯蒂  你一直是巴士司机吗
So, Bertie, have you always been a bus driver?
我之前管理一家鞋店
I used to manage a shoe store.
后来  我辞职了
Then I, uh, quit,
有过几年黑暗的生活
had a few dark years.
-卖过一阵基督徒的T恤  -好吧
- Sold Christian T-shirts for a while. - Okay.
我把输卵管结扎了  可不便宜
Got my tubes tied. Not cheap.
-这谈话真透明  -闭嘴  尼克
- This is a real honest conversation. - Shut up, Nick.
重新振作起来  焕然一新
Pulled myself out of that personal hell, and... voila.
-哇  -我喜欢
- Wow. - You know,
驾驶巴士
I like driving a bus.
可以在仪表盘上放我喜欢的东西
Get to put whatever I want on the dash.
驱走黑暗
Keeps the darkness away.
你明白吗
You know?
我还...
I also, uh...
我在画画
I paint.
你喜欢画画
You paint?
那是艘船
It's a boat.
我能看出来那是条船
Oh, I can see it's a boat.
好吧
All right, well, uh...
我最好把胃药吃了
I better take my stomach medicine.
我三点半就得起床
I got to get up at 3:30.
-早上吗  -我是开公交车的
- Is that a.m.? - I drive a bus.
你就不能闭嘴吃你的破三明治吗  尼克
Will you eat your damn sandwich, Nick.
我不爱吃这个
I don't like it.
你呢  温斯顿  你喜欢吃吗
What about you, Winston? Do you like it?
我不会对你撒谎的  伯蒂
I'm not gonna lie to you, Bertie.
有的地方确实硬得咬不动
Sometimes it was a little hard to chew.
你可以吸一吸让它变软点
Well... you can suck on it to make it soft.
你们俩是擦出火花了吗
Wow. Is something happening between you two?
-伙计  她太真实了  -很好
- Dude, she is so real. - Okay, good.
你能帮我一把吗  你知道你欠我的
Would you do me a favor? Now, you owe me.
温斯顿  我乐意之极  任你差遣
Winston, I would love to. Anything.
说真的  任你差遣
I mean it. Anything.
-那好  -我欠你的
- Okay. - I owe you.
我需要你...
I need you...
今晚帮我把弗格森带回家
...to take Furguson home tonight for me
而我就留在这了
while I just stay here and,
你懂的  碰碰运气
you know, see where this goes.
没问题  这可是重要的一刻
Yes. This is a big moment.
-是啊  -我为你骄傲
- Yeah. - I'm proud of you.
听着  弗格森  我要做成年人该做的事了
Listen, Furguson, I'm about to do what adults do.
-祝我好运吧  -别叽歪了
- Hey, wish me luck. - I think that's enough.
-祝我好运  -这只猫可太肥了
- Wish me luck. - Oh, this is a fat cat.
这决定有点唐突  要不我...
It's a tough decision. Do I...?
我还是走吧
I'll just leave...
-呆着吧  你给我呆着  -好的
- Stay here, stay here. - Okay. Yeah!
希希  等等  请等一下
Cece, wait! Please wait!
我是在和我妈妈发短信
I was texting my mom!
-蠢货  -闭嘴
- Dork. - Shut up!
拜托了
Oh, come on!
你真觉得我会相信你
Do you really expect me to believe that?
不  我保证...  我  我妈妈
No. I-I promise... I... My mom--
她和我发短信是因为我...
she was texting me because I was...
因为我太紧张这次约会了
I was super nervous about this date.
-你妈妈  -你看
- Your mom? - Look.
拿下她们  宝宝
"Go get 'em, Booboo"?
那个指的是我  我是宝宝
That's me. I'm Booboo.
为什么你跟我说话
Why do you need inspirational quotes
还需要你妈妈的励志名言
from your mom just to talk to me?
对不起  我...
I'm sorry. I...
我只是  我刚从一段恋情中走出来
I'm just... I'm coming out of this relationship,
然后有点...  我只是...
and, like... I just...
我不知道  我觉得我不知道怎么...
I don't know. I feel I don't know how to...
我不知道该怎么从头再来了
I don't know how to do this anymore.
我明白你的感觉
I know how you feel.
你明白
You do?
是的
Yeah.
现在我就想给咱俩买几杯酒喝
I just want to buy us some drinking
然后开始对你上下其手  妹子
and get up on you, girl.
你看  你又开始胡言乱语了
You see, you're doing it again.
见鬼  我知道
Damn it! I know.
对不起
Sorry.
斯密特
Hey! Schmidt!
斯密特  你在干什么
Schmidt, what are you doing?!
你拿着那么多巧克力干吗
Why do you have all that chocolate?
我要去把她赢回来
I'm going to go win her back!
你知道我在哪能买到漂亮的蜡烛吗
Do you know where I can get a pretty candle?!
别这样  斯密特  到车上来
No. Come on, Schmidt, get in the car.
上车吧
Get in the car.
我爱她  杰茜
I love her, Jess.
我必须要告诉她
I have to tell her.
你不能
Well, you can't.
你必须放她走
You have to let her go.
我知道
I know.
你说的对  我知道
Look, you're right. I know.
那很好  来吧  上车吧
Okay, good. Come on, get back in the car.
我还知道用不了30秒
I also know that in about 30 seconds,
我会再次从你眼前逃跑
I'm gonna run away from you again,
而且这一次  我会甩掉你
and this time, I will lose you.
我会顺着小巷子  穿过公园
I'll go down alleys, I'll cut across parks.
我会在各种影子里  潜行  躲藏
I will live in the shadows, just slithering, lurking,
穿梭于黑暗之中
trolling the darkness.
杰茜  你只有一种办法阻止我
Jess, there's only one way for you to stop me.
无论是什么  我都会做
Well, I'll do it, whatever it is.
开你的车撞我
Hit me with your car.
什么  不  不
What?! No! No!
那是你阻止我的唯一办法
It's the only way for you to stop me!
不  那太疯狂了  施密特
No! That's crazy, Schmidt!
快  杰茜  就现在  我是活该
Come on, Jess. Now, do it! I deserve it.
我背叛了你最好的朋友
I cheated on your best friend,
我试图让你和尼克分开
I tried to break up you and Nick.
-踩油门  -不
- Hit the gas. - No! No!
杰茜  要么你这么做  要么我就跑了
Jess, you do this, or I'm gonna run.
-我不想这么做  -我数三下
- I don't want to! - I'm gonna give you to the count of three.
-不  我不想  施密特 -三
- No, I don't want to! Schmidt! - Three.
二  为了希希
Two. Do it for Cece.
我的上帝
Oh, my God!
那算什么意思
What the hell was that?!
你让我开车撞你
You told me to hit you with the car!
-你个该死的竟然开车撞我  -你让我撞的
- You friggin' just hit me with your vehicle! - You asked me to.
我没想到你真的会那么干
I didn't think you were really gonna do it.
我就是轻轻碰了你一下
I barely tapped you.
这是我最喜欢的卡其布休闲裤
This is my favorite utility khaki!
那就别在你不想让我开车撞你的时候
Well, then don't tell me to hit you with my car
跟我说让我开车撞你
if you don't want me to hit you with my car!
-你已经失控了  -什么
- You're out of control! - What?
女士  请停到路边
Ma'am, please pull over.
杰茜
Jess!
我的上帝
Oh, my God!
施密特
Schmidt!
混蛋
Son of a bitch!
我知道这看起来像什么
I know what this looks.
像你开车撞人吗
Like you hit a man with your car?
而且是两次
Twice.
我只想撞一次
I only meant to hit you once.
但是你撞了我两次
Well, you hit me twice.
还有  他让我撞他
Also, he asked me to hit him.
我一定是见鬼了
I'm in a really weird place.
我需要写一份报告
I just need to write a report.
她不是罪犯  她
She's not a criminal. She...
她只是在做朋友该做的
She was being a friend.
我撞他是因为我关心他
I hit him because I care about him.
你们两个很奇怪
You guys are into some weird stuff.
祝贺你
Well, congratulations.
你做到了
You made it.
我做到了  不是吗
I did, didn't I?
是的
Yeah.
你知道吗  别担心医院的账单
And, hey, you know, don't worry about the hospital bill.
我会付的
I'll pay it.
等等  你觉得我会付你的
Wait a minute. Did you think that I was gonna pay your...?
你开车撞了我  而且我以为
Well, you hit me with your car, and I thought
-你至少会付那笔钱  -你让我
- you would at least offer. - You told me...
-我以为最好那样  -开车撞你
- I thought it would be a nice... - ...to hit you with the car.
施密特  别假装你没事
Schmidt, don't pretend you're fine.
我知道你有事
I know you're not.
我不好
I'm not fine.
不过会好起来的
But I will be.
我们保持耐心吧
Let's just wait it out.
好的
Okay.
已经半个小时了
God, it's been a half an hour.
喘口气  你们这两个怪物
Come up for air, you weirdoes.
我开始有点兴奋了
I'm getting kind of revved up.
尼克有事儿做了
Nick has some work to do.
给我块巧克力
Give me a chocolate.
-是你  -你好
- Hey, there. - Hey.
我能来点那个吗
Can I get some of that?
你要在这里过夜吗  还是怎样
You spending the night, or what?
当然
Oh, hell, yeah.
翻译：Providence 持久君 卫管小色盲 兮之
翻译：小明漫画家 麦田守望者 扭扭布~V~ MythCretor
时间轴：chance-coco 糖不甩   后期：MythCreator
校对：卫老哥       总监:  丢丢曳